module.exports = [
 {
   question: 'Which of the following properties are measured in Pascals?',
   a: 'Force',
   b: 'Volume',
   c: 'Pressure',
   d: 'Viscosity',
   answer: 'c'
 },
 {
   question: 'What element has the symbol "Co"?',
   a: 'Copper',
   b: 'Chromium',
   c: 'Copernicum',
   d: 'Cobalt',
   answer: 'd'
 },
 {
   question: 'Which scientist is the only person to win Nobel prizes in two different sciences?',
   a: 'Werner Heisenberg',
   b: 'Marie Curie',
   c: 'Nikola Tesla',
   d: 'Rosalind Franklin',
   answer: 'b'
 },
 {
   question: 'What freezes faster: hot water or cold water?',
   a: 'Hot Water',
   b: 'Cold Water',
   c: 'Both Freeze at the Same Rate',
   d: 'The Rate Depends on Location',
   answer: 'a'
 },
 {
   question: 'After distilling his own urine in attempt to create the philosopher\'s stone, what element did Hennig Brand accidentally discover?',
   a: 'Magnesium',
   b: 'Sulfur',
   c: 'Sodium',
   d: 'Phosphorus',
   answer: 'd'
 },
 {
   question: 'What compound is the active component in chili peppers?',
   a: 'Lutein',
   b: 'Capsaicin',
   c: 'Acrylamide',
   d: 'Pyrazine',
   answer: 'b'
 },
 {
   question: 'What kind of technique was used to analyze the composition of soil samples on Mars?',
   a: 'Calorimetry',
   b: 'Chromatography',
   c: 'Isotope Dilution',
   d: 'Spectrometry',
   answer: 'd'
 },
 {
   question: 'Which of the following liquids is the most dense?',
   a: 'Water',
   b: 'Gasoline',
   c: 'Acetone',
   d: 'Chloroform',
   answer: 'd'
 },
 {
   question: 'In 1901, a dental school graduate moved to Colorado Springs and discovered that all of the residents had brown teeth because of this element:',
   a: 'Fluorine',
   b: 'Magnesium',
   c: 'Chlorine',
   d: 'Strontium',
   answer: 'a'
 },
 {
   question: 'What chemical property is a measurement of disorder in a system?',
   a: 'Enthalpy',
   b: 'Gibbs Free Energy',
   c: 'Entropy',
   d: 'Equilibrium Constant',
   answer: 'c'
 },
];